- Come on. Ray-Ray.
- Ray-Ray. man! Come on!
- Do it. motherfucker!
- All right. all right.
- Ray-Ray!
- Do it!
[KNIFE SLICES. BODY THUDS]
I'm sorry. Franklin.
I told you I needed that recipe.
You ain't gonna let Kev kill
him; start a fucking war.
Kev! I can't let this happen.
Kevin!
[GUNSHOT]
Stop! DEA!
What agency doing work in Nicaragua
would want to shut down a DEA operation?
If I'ma tell you about all
this. I'm gonna need a drink.
Kevin dead.
Man. why the fuck did
you have to shoot him?
- Hey. hey.
- [WHISPERS] No.
There's more.
Cops got your name. Franklin.
They know it's you.
You made him this way!
We all made him this way.
- Mama.
- Franklin.
Oh. God. I love you.
I want you to know that
if having you in my life
means that I gotta stop all of this.
then I'ma do that for you. Mama.
Police! Let me see your hands.
- Don't shoot him.
- [INDISTINCT SHOUT]
I'm right here.
- Baby.
- I'm sorry. Mama.
I love you. I love you.
[FLUORESCENT LIGHT HUMMING]
[CHAIN RATTLING]
Lawyer.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
That's him.
No question.
[LIGHT CONTINUES HUMMING]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Place all your personal
effects in the envelope.
When you're done. hand it to the C.O.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Come on. ladies. line up.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Next man up.
- Step forward. inmate.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[FUNKY MUSIC]
Move it. gentlemen.
Let's roll. Step it up.
Go!
Clothes off. We don't have all day.
♪ A junkie walking
through the twilight ♪
Move it! Next man.
♪ I'm on my way home ♪
Get on the bench. Nuts to butts.
Let's go. Move up.
Nuts to butts.
Fuck this shit.
Hey. let's go. Move up.
Man. I ain't doing this bitch-ass shit
so you motherfuckin'
bitch-ass cops can watch.
[SMACKS]
[SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
All of you. stay back!
- [SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
- Fuck you.
Get him out of here.
♪ Home is filled with pain. and it ♪
Keep moving. Keep moving.
♪ Might not be such a bad idea ♪
♪ If I never. never went home again ♪
Spread your cheeks; spread your sacks.
Don't be bashful.
Cough.
[ALL COUGH]
Cough again.
All right. stand up.
♪ And it might not be such
a bad idea if I never ♪
♪ If I never went home
again. home again ♪
♪ Home again. home again ♪
♪ Kick it. quit it. kick it. quit it ♪
♪ Kick it. quit it. kick it ♪
♪ Can't go home again ♪
♪ Home again. home again ♪
[METALLIC THUD]
♪ I can't go home again ♪
[MUFFLED. INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES]
- [DOOR BUZZES]
- All right. listen up. Phone time.
You. you...
And you. Let's go.
I want to make a phone
call. This is bullshit.
Man. you just wait your turn.
Use this phone over here.
You two. over there.
[BUTTONS BEEPING]
[LINE TRILLING]
Hey.
It's me.
You straight?
They got me in Central.
I need you to get J Young down here
as soon as you can. all right?
We gon' get you bail.
Then we gon' fight this
shit from the outside.
Hear me?
Louie and Lee with you?
Louie here.
She send her love.
You talk to your mama?
Nah.
You need anything?
Anything I can do for you?
Listen.
Just get J Young down here. Unc. huh?
Nephew. everything gonna be a'ight.
Yeah.
Yeah. I know.
Love.
Yeah. mm-hmm.
- [MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- What you looking at?
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Hold.
Rack 'em.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Go on.
[METALLIC CLINKING]
- [MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Got fresh meat!
[DOOR BUZZES]
Hold up.
- [DOOR BUZZES]
- Rack 'em.
All right. move out.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Nope.
That's you.
[DOOR THUDS. CLICKS]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey. mon.
Hey.
The government set me up.
They set you up too.
The fuck I tell you about
spouting that crazy-ass shit?
Shut the fuck up 'fore I beat your ass.
[METALLIC THUDDING. SQUEALING]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Rack it.
- [DOOR BUZZES]
[METALLIC CLINKING]
Franklin Saint.
Come with me.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Franklin. how you doing?
Tell me. man.
They charged you with a 187 PC.
Murder one.
Won't know what evidence the state has
until you've been arraigned.
which will be in the next day or two.
We go to court. plead not guilty.
I'll get the discovery.
and then we'll see what
we're dealing with.
Okay?
I need to get the fuck out of here. man.
Make sure I get bail.
It's your first offense.
They'll grant bail.
So you have any more questions for me?
Something you need done in the meantime?
You charge by the hour. right?
Just business. [LAUGHTER]
I'm good.
Well...
[CHUCKLES]
Keep your head up.
See you in two days.
For sure.
Look.
I'm not a fool.
I get that sometimes
there's a bigger picture.
But are you honestly telling me
that the juice on this
bullshit is worth a squeeze?
You know why Nixon started the DEA;
started the war on drugs. right?
It's a dog whistle.
It was intentionally designed
to keep minorities in this country
- on their backs...
- Even if that's true.
it doesn't mean that we
just open the floodgates.
And I respect that you...
that you want to make
a difference. I do.
But you gotta admit that
until people in this
country stop using drugs.
that fighting a war on them
is pointless and costly.
It's unwinnable.
I see.
So your war
is important and noble.
But my war is pointless.
According to the people who
shut down your operation
so that mine can continue.
yeah.
Give me a year...
Or two years. maybe...
Just long enough for us
to give the Nicaraguan
people their democracy back.
And I promise you that at the end of it.
I will hand over every distributor.
every dealer. every supplier
that we work with along the way.
You're gonna make the largest
series of drug-related arrests
that this country has ever seen.
It's the ultimate undercover assignment.
There's no red tape.
There's no oversight.
The results are beyond anything
you could ever possibly imagine.
You should definitely take a
day or two to think it over.
Either way. there's no hard feelings.
At the end of the day...
we're both on the same team.
I'll be in touch.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Rack it.
- [DOOR BUZZES]
[METALLIC CLINKING]
[MEN CHATTERING IN SPANISH]
Hey.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Hey. [SPEAKING SPANISH]
[LAUGHS]
What shoe size are you?
[LAUGHTER]
[MUFFLED. INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- Rack it.
- [DOOR BUZZES]
Come with me.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[MEN JEERING]
Let's go. Move it.
Stay on the line. Keep moving.
All the way.
All right. watch the gate.
Close that up.
There they are.
You all right?
You know. just sit tight.
I'm not sure where you
show up in the lineup.
but I'm right over there. okay?
[GAVEL BANGING]
Court is in session.
Proceeding.
The people versus Oscar Peralta.
Appearances. please?
Yes. counsel for the
defense. Your Honor.
The defendant is present and...
Bail will be set at $20.000.
I have "not guilty" entered.
$60.000.
[INDISTINCT SPEECH]
Bail will be set at $75.000.
[GAVEL BANGS]
The people versus Franklin Saint.
Appearances. please?
Johnson Young. privately retained.
The defendant is in court
and in custody.
Colin Grant for the people. Your Honor.
Mr. Young. how would
you like to proceed?
We waive further reading
of the complaint.
statement of rights. and
enter a plea of not guilty.
and deny all special allegations
and enhancements.
Plea of "not guilty" entered.
Counsel. what are we doing?
Your Honor. can we come back
for a setting date of February 28th?
We're backed up here. Counselor.
We'd be looking at mid-March.
The defense will accept.
Mr. Grant?
Fine by the state.
We will reconvene for
a preliminary hearing
on the 12th of March.
Bail will be set at $75.000.
Please the court. Your
Honor. at this time.
the state would ask that bail be denied.
On what grounds?
A DEA agent has identified the
defendant as the shooter.
The defendant fled the scene.
and when he was finally apprehended.
he was driving a vehicle
not in his name.
he had thousands of
dollars of cash on him.
along with a fake driver's license.
Your Honor. we believe Mr. Saint
could pose a significant flight risk.
Your Honor. this young man has no priors
and has no reason to run.
And what kid under the
age of 21 years of age
doesn't have a fake ID?
Your Honor. the defense
implores Her Honor
to follow her instincts
and grant bail.
I'm persuaded by the people's argument.
Bail is denied.
The defendant will be transferred
to Pitchard Detention Facility
where he will remain in
custody until his trial.
[GAVEL BANGS]
Y'all happy now?
Got the black man in chains
over selling a goddamn dime bag.
I say y'all motherfuckers happy now?
Shut the fuck up.
You'll make this trip in an ambulance.
Yessa. massa.
I's understand.
Oh. you making jokes?
And what the fuck are you looking at?
Boss.
Let's go. Let's get a move on.
Two and two!
All right. you heard the man.
Move it.
[BRAKES HISS]
[BUZZER BUZZES]
Move. Let's go.
[BUZZER BUZZING RHYTHMICALLY]
Face forward.
Eyes straight ahead.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[BUZZER BUZZING RHYTHMICALLY]
Two by two. Let's go.
[DOOR BUZZING]
Eyes front. gentlemen. Let's go.
[DOOR BUZZES]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[DOOR BUZZES. CLANKS]
Fuckin' looking at me?
Fuck! [SMACKS]
[SMACKING AND GRUNTING.
MEN CHATTERING EXCITEDLY]
[MEN CHEERING]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey. down there! Fresh
fish coming in. y'all!
That's the one I want.
[MEN JEERING]
Rest tonight. boys.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[MEN JEERING]
Tonight's getting kind of low.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Motherfucker.
Hey. nigga.
Hey.
Ray-Ray.
I knew I wasn't tripping.
[LAUGHTER]
I used to chop it up with
this boy back on the block.
Hey. that boy got game for real.
Fuck they bring you in here on?
Some bullshit.
Bet that.
Same shit with me.
Couple months on some nonsense.
Shit ain't about nothing. though.
Food ain't shit. but at least
we ain't breaking up rocks all day.
Man. look.
I know we ain't see eye-to-eye.
but in here. we from the same hood.
So we gotta stick together.
Yeah.
All right. cool.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Hey. cuz. get this nigga a pack.
Stay up. man.
Give 'em dice. some got bank.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[LOUD METALLIC THUD]
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
Come here. man. [SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
Payback time.
[SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
Shut up. nigga. Shut the fuck up.
This one for Lenny. motherfucker.
Thought I was gonna let it slide. bitch?
[SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
Motherfucker.
[SMACKS. FRANKLIN GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Franklin Saint?
There's someone here to see you.
Goddamn. Nephew.
Yeah.
Making friends in here.
Goddamn Mexicans?
Don't tell me a brother did this shit.
Ray-Ray in here.
Apparently. he ain't happy about Lenny.
All right. Ray-Ray.
Hmm?
You tell him I know where
his goddamn family live.
I'll kill everybody that
motherfucker ever knew.
You hear me?
Want some goddamn pharaoh
Ten Commandments
type shit on his ass.
- Just stop.
- Shit. you hear me?
Stop.
Goddamn lawyer. Johnson.
say he gonna get you out
on that fuckin' bail.
Some writ... write? Some shit.
It don't matter.
Fuck you mean it don't matter?
We'll get you out of there.
Your auntie. she was gonna
come up here and see you too.
but they only let two people at
a time in this motherfucker.
She gonna come up this weekend.
It's gonna be all right. Unc.
Huh?
Here. nigga.
What's good. homey?
What's up. man?
They ain't come at you?
Nah.
Seen Wanda?
I'm sorry. man.
You tried to keep her out the cookhouse.
Should have listened.
But I want you to listen to me.
I been where you at. nigga.
But you gotta keep
fighting. you hear me?
Yeah. man. Of course.
'Cause this shit ain't your fault.
Lee. no. Stop.
When you leave here.
go back in that dorm;
grab the first nigga you see.
and beat the fuck out that nigga
till they grab you off of that nigga.
You hear me?
Show 'em who the fuck you is. nigga!
- All right.
- No! Look at this nigga face. man!
- Fuck!
- All right. come on.
Show 'em who the fuck you is!
Any nigga that motherfuckin' try you.
- beat the fuck out that nigga!
- All right. come on.
Show 'em who the fuck you is. nigga!
- Come on.
- Fuck that phone. nigga.
[RECEIVER PARTS CLATTERING]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Don't be holding out on us.
Look at this nigga.
[FABRIC TEARING]
[LOUD METALLIC THUD]
[BODY THUDS]
[GAGGING. CHOKING]
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
All right. listen up.
[SHUSHING]
Daniel Martinez.
Anthony Hill.
Miguel Chavez.
Franklin Saint.
Brian Getz.
Darius Coleman.
Jesús Morales.
Up front. Let's go.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey. Mama.
Alton.
What... what?
She can't keep her shit together?
Tell her to get the fuck out of here.
I don't need this shit right now.
Hold on. Hold on.
Huh?
The fuck. I don't
fucking need this shit.
Okay.
[CLEARS THROAT]
How you doing. man?
[CHUCKLES]
Never in a million years
would have thought
the two of you would be like this.
Whole goddamn world's
turned upside down.
Yeah. I can't imagine how
strange it must be for you
after all this time.
I know there ain't much I can say to you
or that. uh...
or that you want to hear.
But I know something about this.
Um...
- And...
- Listen. I need you to stop.
And there is always something
left on the inside.
I said stop.
No matter how much you
think there ain't.
I don't fuckin' need this
shit right now. you hear me?
I don't fuckin' need it.
You wait till fuckin'
now. till I'm in here
to be a fuckin' dad? [LAUGHS]
- It's a bad fuckin' joke. man.
- Stop it. son.
It's a bad fuckin' joke!
- How the fuck you come back...
- [DOOR BUZZES]
Franklin. stop.
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- [INDISTINCT SPEECH]
Get the fuck away from me!
Stop. Franklin.
Calm down. baby.
Man. don't fuckin' come back!
You were never fuckin' there for me!
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- Franklin! Don't hurt him. please!
Move it. Get in there!
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Motherfucker! [SMACKS]
[SMACKING AND GRUNTING]
[MEN CHEERING]
[BUZZER BUZZING RHYTHMICALLY]
- [GUN COCKS]
- Get the fuck off of me.
[BUZZING AND CHEERING CONTINUE]
[BUZZING CONTINUES DISTANTLY]
[METALLIC THUD]
Hey! Wake the fuck up.
Let's go.
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Just kept setting on that nigga. homey.
Every time. homey.
Nigga owe me magazines too.
They let this nigga out
the infirmary already.
He coming over.
You asked me why I'm in here. right?
I killed my best homey.
And my people on the outside.
they know your family stay
off of West and 48th.
Your grandma.
mama.
little baby sister.
About this high. right?
Any y'all little niggas
step to me again.
and I'll kill all your fuckin' families.
[LAUGHS]
You know I mean business.
Don't forget about Winnie.
[LINE TRILLING]
Hey.
This is a collect call from
Pitchard Detention Center.
Will you accept charges?
All right.
Hey. Put Louie on.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
You must be Reed.
And you're Louie.
Thanks for coming.
Franklin said you don't like the phone.
You want to tell me what this is about?
Since the arrest. we
ain't had no problems.
DEA don't seem to care one
bit about our business.
And Franklin. he want us
to keep going without him.
But he said you might
need some convincing.
Yeah.
As usual. Franklin's right.
Look.
I know that boy is special.
I've known it his whole life.
But he sent me here.
so maybe he think I'm
something special too.
What are we talking about here?
About you running things
while he's in jail?
I will if I have to.
But I think the best option
for everybody involved
is to get Franklin out of there.
Now. he said you a man with connects.
influence;
might be able to help.
With a murder charge.
Well. what about approaching the judge.
getting him out on bail?
He also mentioned this DEA
agent who saw the shooting.
Now. our lawyer seem to think
that she the only witness they got.
So...
if she went away.
- that put the hurt on they case.
- Went away?
Them Franklin words. not mine.
I'm sorry. I can't help you with this.
And...
as far as continuing
things without Franklin.
you're just gonna have to give
me more time to think about it.
Look.
This is new territory for me.
And personally. I think
Franklin is crazy for this ask.
But he seem to think that y'all two
got some sort of bond or
vision for the future.
But for me. this about
getting my nephew.
who I love more than
anything in this world.
out of that prison.
So if there is anything that you can do.
do it.
You know. I love the views
in this city. man.
Where I come from. the land
is so flat. there's no...
there's no changes to it.
There's no levels to it.
We only deal in cocaine.
No heroin.
No marijuana.
Pure product that only
rich people can afford.
Agreed.
And we keep a close eye
on all the players.
I'm not letting LA turn into Miami.
Of course.
And you promise me when it's done.
I take down all the dealers.
Every one.
I must be fuckin' insane.
You ready to get started?
So... [CLEARS THROAT]
there are coincidences.
and then there's fate.
And then there's what
I'm about to tell you.
And it's gonna sound real strange.
but just know that I
wouldn't be asking it
if it wasn't vital.
Okay.
A couple weeks ago. you
witnessed a murder
in Acuña Park.
It's a young black kid.
He allegedly shot a friend of
his to prevent a gang war.
There's nothing alleged about it.
I saw the whole thing.
I sat with the kid while he bled out.
How do you know about that?
All that matters right now
is that you go to the detective
who's working the case
and you recant your statement.
Tell him you're mistaken
on what you saw.
You're serious.
To take back a statement?
I could face charges.
- No.
- Perjury.
No. no. no. As of right now.
you're still a federal officer.
They're not gonna like it.
but they'll let it go.
This kid. who is he to you?
He's just important to me... for now.
- Franklin.
- Mr. Young.
You got something for me?
[CHUCKLES]
You're going home.
[DOOR BUZZES. SQUEALS. CLANKS]
Haven't been getting much
sleep since I got out.
No shock. I know.
What's strange is. it ain't the beatings
I see in my dreams.
It's not Ray-Ray.
not the dude who hung himself.
not the bars.
not the guards.
It's Reed Thompson.
Welcome back.
Thanks to you.
I got lucky.
Was that it?
Luck?
Two nights ago. I went
to Avi's hotel room...
Gave him $80.000 cash;
told him it was reparations.
I wouldn't say he was happy to see me.
but the motherfucker always
had a soft spot for me.
[LAUGHS]
So when I went back hat in hand.
he agreed to hear me out.
Told him about Reed.
how he got me off a murder charge.
A man like that is someone to fear.
Remember our conversation in the bank?
Your speech about control?
You were wrong. Reed.
My mistake was giving
Kevin too much room.
'Cause we were boys.
But now I know.
There's only one way to do things.
Anybody fuck with the program.
break a rule. they out.
Don't matter who.
Sounds like you're ready to
get this started back up.
Suppose I gotta be. right?
I mean. you ain't get me out
'cause you enjoy our conversations.
Yeah.
I guess that's right.
[LAUGHS]
I'm ready when you are. Reed.
You see. for years.
the U.S. been fighting a
covert war in Nicaragua.
trying to stop the Communists.
Avi's been smuggling foreign-made arms
from the Middle East to
Panama on Reed's behalf.
We talking tens of millions
of dollars' worth...
Enough to fight an entire fuckin' war.
I don't think our Mr. Reed Thompson's
just some drug dealer.
I think he works for the government.
And now...
well. I think we work for him.
[FUNKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
♪ Cold. cold eyes. upon me they stare ♪
♪ People all around me.
and they're all in fear ♪
♪ They don't seem to want
me. but they won't admit ♪
♪ I must be some kind of creature ♪
♪ Up here having fits ♪
♪ From my party house. I'm
afraid to come outside ♪
♪ Although I'm filled with love ♪
♪ I'm afraid they'll hurt my pride ♪
♪ So I play the part I
feel they want of me ♪
♪ And I pull the shades so I
won't see them seein' me ♪
♪ Havin' hard times in this crazy town ♪
♪ Havin' hard times ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm